

STEFAN BRUNOTTE

Junior Full Stack Developer C# https://stefanbrunotte.azurewebsites.net/

About me

Are you looking for an entry-level C# developer that is multi-talented with lots of experience from different fields? Well, here is a great opportunity – meet me, Stefan Brunotte.

I am a junior full stack developer with C# as my main language. When combining my scholar qualifications with my work experience you will find a person with great people skills, and great knowledge both from the banking/trading-real estate areas, and service fields.

I see myself as a senior C# developer in 5 years, within these years I have developed a stable and solid knowledge base that will make me capable of jumping into complex code that will meet customer/employer expectations. As an employer you will get a hard-working asset that is focused on delivering the best possible work!

Most Significant Experience

All projects can be viewed at https://stefanbrunotte.azurewebsites.net/ all code is available at my GitHub page: https://github.com/MrBrunotte

Lexicon C# ASP.NET Core MVC 20/08/20 - 15/01/21

C# ASP .NET Core MVC 7 module course.

The modules cover:

C#, ASP .NET Core MVC Framework, Web applications, Database (Entity Framework), Testing, REST API, SCRUM, Azure AZ-900 certification (Azure).

Experience gained:

Throughout the course I have gained a good understanding of the underlying pillars of OOP and C# as a language. The projects in the course have given me a good understanding of ASP.NET Core framework and Visual Studio. I am now able to build full stack web applications using C# and ASP.NET Core Framework including Entity framework and MySQL. When building the project, we followed the SCRUM framework.

Code Institute, Dublin Ireland

Full Stack Developer

02/2019 - 06/2020

Fully remote course that covered: Front-, Backend and Database management.

Covered in course:

Python, JavaScript, jQuery, Django and Flask frameworks, MongoDB, SQLite, Heroku Postgres, Heroku deployment, Bootstrap, Materialize, APIs.

Experience gained:

Throughout the course I learned to work remotely and independently. The course covered all three aspect of a Full Stack Web Developer. Three projects were deployed during the course and they are available at my homepage.

Stockholm School of Economics Master Banking & Finance

08/2009 - 06/2011

Advanced theories and methods of financial analysis.

Covered in course:

Portfolio Theory, Corporate Finance, Financial Derivatives, Fixed Income Securities, Econometrics, Master Dissertation in Finance.

Experience gained:

Both theoretical and practical of finance in a global context, the program also gave me a solid foundation to stand on in my private day trading career. This will also benefit me as a developer since I have a good knowledge of this industry.

Skills & Tools

Main Language

C#

ASP .NET Core MVC

- Entity Framework
- LINO
- **REST API**

Other language Python

Django

Flask

JavaScript HTML5 CSS3

Database

MySQL MonaoDB

Heroku Postgres

Version Control

Git GitHub

Cloud

Azure **AWS**

IDF

Visual Studio 2019 Visual Studio Code

Frameworks

SCRUM Bootstrap Materialize

Programs/UX

Adobe Xd DrawIO

Academic Qualification

AZ-900 Fundamentals

Microsoft Azure Fundamentals

C# ASP .NET Core MVC

Lexicon

7-module course ASP .NET Core MVC

Full Stack Developer

Code Institute. Dublin Ireland Frontend, Backend, & Database management

Programming 1 Basic C#

Komvux course Basic C# concepts

Master Banking & Finance

Stockholm School of Economics Portfolio Theory, Corporate Finance, Financial Derivatives, Fixed Income Securities, Econometrics, Master Dissertation in Finance. **Time Line**

← 12/2020 - 01/2021

08/2020 - 01/2021

01/2005 - Current →

04/2005 - Current →

02/2019 - 06/2020

04/2015 - 11/2018 →

08/2018 - 09/2018

05/2014 - 11/2014 →

08/2009 - 06/2011

Work Experience

Developer

Developer at Prog-It AB Maintaining and updating clients webpages

Discretionary Futures Day Trader

Private trading of my own funds Part-time day trader (own) trading Futures with my own discretionary TA-analysis

Care Assistant

Attendo IOF

Management, supervision, and support for

Unaccompanied minors.

Real Estate Agent

Siw Kraft Mäkleri AB

Real Estate Agent

Real estate agent selling high-end Penthouses in Stockholm

Bachelor of Science, Business Adm.

Stockholm School of Economics Political economy, Bachelor thesis, and other related courses

Estate Agent Program

Gävle Högskola

Phone:

Email:

Basic estate agency, sales and marketing, tax law

+46 708-240 243

mrbrunotte@gmail.com

← 01/2008 - 06/2009

03/2005 - 06/2007 →

03/2003 - 03/2005

Erik Olsson Fastighetsförmedling Real estate agent selling both houses and apartments in the Stockholm metropolitan

Store owner Birger Jarlsgatan 37

Salary, management, inventory, personnel

area

01/2000 - 08/2003 → 7-eleven Franchisee

Real estate agent selling both houses and Contact apartments in the Stockholm metropolitan area. All different store owner duties:

Junior Full Stack Developer

Stefan Brunotte

Portfolio: https://stefanbrunotte.azurewebsites.net/

> GitHub: https://github.com/MrBrunotte

www.linkedin.com/in/stefan-brunotte Reference: On request LinkedIn: